http://www.accucap.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
SoftwareAccuCapStenoVoiceSteno and VoiceStudentBridge MobileEclipseStenoVoiceSteno and VoiceEditStudentScopingStudentEclipse Student SoftwareStudent 90-Day TrialSearchMasterWritersPassport TouchAccessoriesSkinsPassport SkinsPassport Touch SkinsWriter Care & Protection PlansPassportPassport TouchLaptopsFujitsu U939 - 13.3"U939 - i5/512GB - BlackU939 - i5/512GB - RedU939 - i7/1TB - BlackU939 - i7/1TB - RedThinkBook 14 IIL - 14"Thinkpad X1 Carbon - 14"AccessoriesKeyboardsServicesSpecialsFeaturedClearanceConference Bundle w/FREE
Bridge SubscriptionStudent 90-Day TrialCatalogAudioMicrophonesUSBSpeech RecognitionSTENO SR PRO-1STENO SR PRO-2Andrea Pure Audio USB Sound CardMuffleMittHands Free StrapHeadphonesLong Corded EarbudsProfessional HeadphonesSplittersAudio Jack SplitterUSB-A Audio SplitterUSB-C Audio SplitterCables & ConnectionCablesSerial10 Foot Realtime Cable15 Foot Realtime CableCIC Cable Kit for 5 Receiving ComputersCIC Cable for 1 Receiving ComputerUSB-A Serial AdapterUSB-C Serial AdapterCarrying CasesDeluxe Writer CasePassport (Gen 1) Writer CaseDVD DriveFlash DrivesHubs4-Port Ultra Slim w/2ft Cable5-in-1 USB C Hub | .5 ft5-in-1 USB Hub | .5 ft | Type-A5-in-1 USB Hub | 2.5ft5-in-1 USB-C Hub | 2.5 ftType C to Type A AdapterMemory CardsSD Cards64GBmicroSD CardsCard ReadersPower SupplyTraining & EducationVideo TutorialsWebinar RecordingsWorkbooksRealtime Voice Writing - 9th EditionUSB DevicesExternal USB DevicesWirelessBluetooth AdapterRouter w/Battery (black)Router w/Battery (white)USB Powered RouterWorking Remotely AccessoriesWebinars & TrainingGetting StartedWatch Past WebinarsAccuCAPAccuCap - Captioning Made Easy CEU RequestCatch-UpCatch-Up Webinar CEU RequestEclipse EmpowermentCEU RequestEclipseVox Basics BootcampEclipse Vox w/Bettye KeyesHot TopicsHyperkeysHyperkeys CEU RequestSpooktacular NumbersSpooktacular Numbers CEU RequestWorking w/Eclipse Remotely (ZOOM)Purchase Past Webinars2020 Eclipse MasterclassAccuCapPandemic Terminology Specialist Training WebinarCatch-UpEclipseVox Basics BootcampEclipseVox w/Bettye KeyesHot TopicsHyperkeysSpooktacular NumbersEclipse EmpowermentMaterialsWorkbooksEclipse 9 Advanced WorkbookEclipse 9 Basic WorkbookVideo TutorialsEclipse Basics - FREEPandemic Terminology WebinarWorking with Eclipse Remotely - ZOOMMore...Private TrainingAuthorized TrainersSupportDownloadsBridge MobilePassportUtilities and MoreFree SoftwareEmail Tech SupportSoftware Support PlansRemote SupportEmail Invoice RequestPay Per IncidentContact UsFinancingSalesEmail Tech SupportCOVID-19 UpdateAbout Us
Catalog
AudioMicrophonesUSBSpeech RecognitionSTENO SR PRO-1STENO SR PRO-2Andrea Pure Audio USB Sound CardMuffleMittHands Free StrapHeadphonesLong Corded EarbudsProfessional HeadphonesSplittersAudio Jack SplitterUSB-A Audio SplitterUSB-C Audio SplitterCables & ConnectionCablesSerial10 Foot Realtime Cable15 Foot Realtime CableCIC Cable Kit for 5 Receiving ComputersCIC Cable for 1 Receiving ComputerUSB-A Serial AdapterUSB-C Serial AdapterCarrying CasesDeluxe Writer CasePassport (Gen 1) Writer CaseDVD DriveFlash DrivesHubs4-Port Ultra Slim w/2ft Cable5-in-1 USB C Hub | .5 ft5-in-1 USB Hub | .5 ft | Type-A5-in-1 USB Hub | 2.5ft5-in-1 USB-C Hub | 2.5 ftType C to Type A AdapterMemory CardsSD Cards64GBmicroSD CardsCard ReadersPower SupplyTraining & EducationVideo TutorialsWebinar RecordingsWorkbooksRealtime Voice Writing - 9th EditionUSB DevicesExternal USB DevicesWirelessBluetooth AdapterRouter w/Battery (black)Router w/Battery (white)USB Powered RouterWorking Remotely Accessories
You are hereHome » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy The following statement discloses the consumer privacy practices of Advantage Software Corporation ("Advantage") for the Advantage Web Site (this "Site"). This Privacy Policy governs all use of this Site.
If you do not consent to these privacy practices, do not use this Site or download any materials from it. We do revise and update our privacy practices from time to time. In general, we do not provide specific notification of such updates, and we reserve the right make them without any notice to you. You should visit this page, at least once every thirty days, to review our then-current privacy practices, because they are binding on you. All updates will be published at this site. Your continued use of this Site shall be considered your consent to any revised privacy practices. Your Privacy Use of Personally Identifiable Information In general, you can visit this Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, most areas of this Site require registration to access, which requires you to provide certain personally identifiable information, including: your name, mailing address, email address and voice and/or fax telephone numbers. We collect this information to better understand your needs and provide you with services that are valuable to you. If you choose not to provide some of the information we request, you can still visit much of this Site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers and services such as downloading trial or evaluation software. Advantage provides a number of ways for you to "opt-out" of receiving certain additional information from us or having us provide your personal information to our partners. We may offer you these choices at the time you give us your information. However, the availability of certain offers and services such as downloading trial or evaluation software may be conditioned upon your agreement to permit Advantage or our business partners to contact you, in which case, notice of any such condition will appear on this Site. Please be advised that in certain instances, it may be necessary for Advantage to disclose your personal information to federal, state and local government officials in the U.S. or overseas or otherwise as required by our legal obligations. Personal data privacy is a new and evolving area, and mistakes and miscommunication are possible. We will do our best to maintain the accuracy of your personal information. To make changes to our records of your personal information, please modify your registration profile. Use of Cookies Advantage may use cookies from time to time. Cookies are small text files a Web site can use to recognize a repeat visitor to the Web site. We use cookies for various reasons. Cookies enable us to provide you with a better experience by allowing us to understand what areas of this Site are of interest to our members. These cookies do not track individual information. Cookies from Advantage can only be read by Advantage Web sites. If you do not want Advantage to deploy cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a Web site tries to put a cookie in your browser software. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you can still access most of this Site, however, your ability to use some of the products and/or services at this Site may be affected. Password When you register with this Site, you will be provided a password that will allow you to access this Site. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your personal information and password. You shall be responsible for all uses of your password, whether or not authorized by you. You agree to immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your password. Links to Third Party Web Sites At this Site, there may be links to companies with whom we have a relationship. Advantage is not responsible for the privacy practices of our business partners. We encourage you to read their privacy statements, as they may differ from ours. Please remember that any information you submit in a chat group or forum will be deemed public information and is not confidential. There is a risk in such communication venues that information can be collected and used by others. Please be careful and responsible when you are online. Questions regarding this Privacy Statement please contact us.
